

Personal

Name Mokuoane Sidney Ramphalile

Address

Available upon request.

Phone number

+27 83 666 9423

Fmail

sidneyramphalile@gmail.com

Date of birth

05-03-1997

Gender

Male

Nationality

South African

Marital status

Single

Driving licence

Drivin C1

Website

https://github.com/SidneyRamphalile

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sidney-ramphalile/

Interests

HTML and CSS coding

Python Programming

Playing the acoustic guitar

Learning new skills

Languages

English Fluent

Sesotho Native

Mokuoane Sidney Ramphalile

I am an optimistic, ambitious, hardworking individual with a great passion for people. I have excellent communication skills. I am an Electrical Engineering graduate with a keen interest in technology. I am establishing myself as a competent and skilled engineer, to strive to uphold the good image of the organization, to always execute my duties in a responsible, punctual, and loyal manner, to develop my knowledge within the Environmental Sector and all areas of expertise, skills, and experience to further the objectives of my employer and to contribute effectively to the function of the organization that I work for through efficient and effective dedication to my work.

Education and Qualifications

National Diploma: Electrical Engineering Feb 2016 - Oct

Central University of Technology, Free State, Bloemfontein 2021

National Senior Certificate (Matric)

Jan 2011 - Nov

HTS Louis Botha, Bloemfontein 2015

Work experience

In-Service Training

Sep 2020 - Jun 2021

Tsotellang Construction & trading (Pty)Ltd, Bloemfontein

Engineering Trainee. Compulsory practical work in order to obtain my National Diploma qualification. House wiring, Geyser Installations, and Wiring, Electrical Distribution Board Wiring, Wall-cutting, and house tubbing, Installation of LED, and fluorescent light bulbs.

Jan 2020 - Feb 2020

In-Service Training

RWK ELECTRICAL (PTY) LTD, Bloemfontein

Engineering Trainee. Compulsory practical work in order to obtain my National Diploma qualification. Digging Trenches, Laying underground cables, replacing 4x4 socket plugs, removing old wire, and replacing it with a new one.

Peer Mentor

May 2019 - Oct 2019

Central University of Technology, Free State, Bloemfontein

Mentoring first-year students, providing information, guidance, and encouragement, helping them prepare for the professional world, and advising them on how to make a successful transition from high school to their first year on campus.

Volunteer Jun 2019 - Jun 2019

At Service ICT Company, Bloemfontein

Create cable routes, wire an electrical socket in parallel, correctly tighten electrical wires, use ladders safely, use safety equipment, install trunking, use power tools – drill and mini grinder and handle wires properly when unwinding and installing.

Registrations Assistant

Jan 2019 - Feb 2019

Central University of Technology, Free State, Bloemfontein

Assisting the Central University of Technology during their registration and being part of the orientation for the first-year students.

Skills

Microsoft Word, Excel and Powerpoint

Responsive Web Design



Computer Literacy	
Python	
Peer Mentoring	
Teaching	
House Wiring	

Short Courses

Google IT Support Professional Certificate Coursera	Jul 2021 - Dec 2022
TOTAL: CompTIA A+ Certification (220-1001) Udemy	Nov 2021 - Dec 2022
TOTAL: CompTIA A+ Certification (220-1002) Udemy	Jan 2023 - Jan 2023
Responsive Web Design Free Code Camp	Apr 2021 - Jun 2021
Diploma in Python Programming Alison	Apr 2020 - Apr 2020
Diploma in Electrical Studies - Revised 2017 Alison	Sep 2019 - May 2020
Word Essential Training (Office 365/Microsoft 365) LinkedIn Learning	Oct 2022 - Oct 2022
Excel Essential Training (Office 365/Microsoft 365) LinkedIn Learning	Oct 2022 - Oct 2022
Learning PowerPoint Desktop (Office 365/Microsoft 365) LinkedIn Learning	Oct 2022 - Oct 2022

Achievements

- 1. Best Peer Mentor in the Faculty of Engineering, Built Environment, and Information Technology 2019.
- 2. SAIEE (South African Institute of Electrical Engineers) Student Member 2019.
- 3. Committed and active member of the Electrical and Computer systems Academic Association (ECSAA) student organization at the Central University of Technology 2018.

References

Mrs. Zanete Malan	Central University of Technology,
082 805 0591	Free State
zmalan@cut.ac.za	

Mr. Barco Van RhjinAt Service ICT082 507 7724companybarco@atservice.co.zacompany

Dr. Anesu Ruswa Accenture 071 341 7598

anesu.ruswa@accenture.com